lboro.ac.uk 2017-12-11

# Loughborough University

At Loughborough University we believe strongly in protecting our users' privacy. We will not wilfully disclose information about our users to any third party without first receiving our users' consent.

This Privacy Policy sets out the privacy practices for the services offered on any Loughborough University owned and/or operated websites ("the Website").

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

View the [privacy policy](https://www.lboro.ac.uk/alumni/privacy/) for the Alumni Association.

## Your Personal Information

All personal information you provide via the Website will be treated as private and confidential. Please see any pages where information is collected for further relevant information.

Loughborough University may compile data in aggregate form so that Loughborough University may better understand users that visit the Website. Aggregate data is anonymous and does not contain any personal information that identifies users.

## Sharing of Information

Loughborough University will not sell, rent, trade or give away any user's personal information or email lists to third parties without first obtaining the user's consent.

The Website contains links to other websites. Loughborough University is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or the content of such websites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Security

Loughborough University is committed to the security of our users' personal information and we have security procedures in place to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under Loughborough University's control.

## Cookies

See our [Cookies page](https://www.lboro.ac.uk/cookies.html) for more information about our cookie use and how you can restrict or block cookies.

## Capturing of Personal Information outside the European Economic Area

From time to time Loughborough University may capture and process personal information outside the European Economic Area. When this is done Loughborough University will endeavour to comply with the requirements of any local data protection laws. In any event Loughborough University will capture and process such personal information in accordance with the requirements set out in the Data Protection Act 1998.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about Loughborough University's Privacy Policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied to Loughborough University, please e-mail the [Data Protection Officer](mailto:dp@lboro.ac.uk) or write to The Data Protection Officer at Academic Registry, Loughborough University, Loughborough, Leics, UK LE11 3TU.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the above address.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

© 2017 Loughborough University. All rights reserved.
